Guide to the Evan Rupert Nash Collection, 1827-1945
Department of Special Collections
- 1866 - 1869 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2. 1866, Feb. 18.John S. Freeman to [Seymour W.] Nash.
  - 33. 1866, Feb. 24.Mrs. C. E. Baker to Seymour W. Nash. About herself and Wallingford.
  - 4. 1866, Mar. 28.John S. Freeman to [Seymour W. Nash]. Brother's illness.
  - 5. 1866, Apr. 10.[Harriett] A. Noyes to Seymour W. Nash. New teeth.
  - 6. 1866, Apr. 11.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Family news, death of Noah McNitt, her husband not in sympathy with Community.
  - 7. 1866, Apr. 23.Mrs. C. E. Baker to Seymour W. Nash. Mr. & Mrs. Smith, inquires about Sarah B. Nash, people at Wallingford.
  - 8. 1866, May [24].George Cragin to Seymour W. Nash. John S. Freeman's application to join Community.
  - 9. 1866, June 4.John S. Freeman to [S. W. Nash]. Plans to go to Oneida on trial.
  - 10. 1866, July 16.John S. Freeman to [S. W. Nash]. Grandmother ill, mother returned from Oneida.
  - 11. 1866, Aug. [8].Wealthy Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Family & neighborhood news, George Loomis.
    9/4
  - 12. 1866, Sept. 5.[W. Atwood and Deborah Knowles] to Seymour & Sarah Nash. Family news.
  - 13. 1866, Sept. 23.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Personal & family, 40 yrs. since they gave themselves to God, Mrs. E. P. Freeman.
    9/23
  - 14. 1866, Dec. 2.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Atwood has returned from Community, Mercy to be married.
  - 15. 1867, Jan. 13.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Egbert's twins.
  - 16. [1867, Jan.].Unknown to Unknown. Egbert's twins.
  - 17. [1867], Mar. 6.W. Atwood Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash?]. A note not addressed.
    1/2 1/5 1/13 5/15
  - 18. 1867, Mar. 18.Deborah [Knowles] to Sarah [B. Nash].
  - 19. 1867, Apr. 5.W. Atwood Knowles to [Seymour & Sarah Nash]. Family problems.
    4/1
  - 20. 1867, Apr. 24.W. Atwood Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash].
    6/9
  - 21. 1867, July 7.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash].
  - 22. 1867, July 10.Ellen [Nash?] to Edwin S. Nash. Father ill. (Daniel P.?)
    20
  - 23. 1867, July 21.[Deborah Knowles] to Sarah [B. Nash]. Asks price of fruits.
  - 24. [1867], Sept. [7].Alice [Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Willow Place, trap makers, father's illness.
  - 25. 1867, Sept. 24.Olive [Ann Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Mrs. Hawley father's nurse, Uncle Seymour, H. M. W. Rilla and Mrs. Skinner.
  - 26. 1867, Dec. 8.Deborah W. Knowles to Seymour [W. Nash]. Personal, note by Atwood.
    11/2 [UNK]
  - 27. [1867], Dec. 12.W. Atwood Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash].
  - 28.a 1867, [Dec.] 27.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Christmas celebration, Atwood, Mr. Freeman.
  - 29. 1868, Jan. 25.[Deborah Knowles] to Seymour [W. Nash]. Personal, earthquake, Atwood, Singer sewing machine.
    [UNK] [UNK] [UNK]
  - 30.a 1868, Mar. 3.Deborah W. Knolwes to Seymour [W. Nash]. Atwood.
  - 31. 1868, Apr. 5.Deborah W. Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. Personal & note on scrap of paper.
  - 32. [1868], Aug. 2.Deborah W. Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash].
  - 33.a 1868, Oct. 13.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Sarah Knowles married, Egbert McNitt.
  - 34. 1868, Nov. 29.[Charles] Olds to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 35. 1868, Dec. 17.Erminia Nash Worcester to Seymour W. Nash. Family news since death of husband in 1859, Daniel (death?).
  - 36. 1868, Dec. 20.C[harles] Olds to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 37. 1869, Mar. 18.Erminia Nash Worcester to [Seymour W. Nash]. Family news, war occurrances.
  - 38. [1869], Apr. 22.[Florilla Nash] to Edwin S. Nash Chess, duties, lessons.
  - 39. 1869, Oct. 14.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Personal & family news.
- 1870-1876 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1. 1870, Jan. 6.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Family news.
  - 2. 1870, Mar. 6.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash].
  - 3. 1870, Apr. 17.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. There seems to be a great stir in the world, about the OC...
  - 4. 1870, [Aug.] 5.Thaxter Poole to [Seymour W. Nash]. History of the Poole family.
  - 5. 1871, Apr. 27.Thaxter [UNK] to [Seymour W. Nash]. Flowers.
  - 6. 1871, May 5.Harriet [UNK] to [Seymour W. Nash]. News of Wallingford, death of Mr. Allen.
  - 7. 1871, Sept. 4.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Family news.
  - 8. 1872, Jan. 15.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. Death of Sarah [B. Nash].
  - 9. 1872, Mar. 23.E. Higgins to Seymour W. Nash. Written to Wallingford.
  - 10. 1872, Mar. 27.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash. Uriah Church dies, visit uncle Thaxter Poole.
  - 11. 1872, Apr. [14].E. Higgins and B.T.T. to Seymour W. Nash. Seymour's fall.
  - 12. 1872, May 8.Mrs. L. E. Kelly to Seymour W. Nash. News of Oneida.
  - 13. 1872, May 12.E. Higgins to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 14. 1872, May 19.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash. News of Community & Elinor.
  - 15. [1872], May 22.Erastus A. V [UNK] to [S. W.] Nash. Mr. Kelly hurt, Seymour hurt leg in fall.
    5/26/72
  - 16. 1872, June 16.Mrs. E. H. Allen to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 17. 1872, July 27.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash. Aunt Erminia's death.
  - 18. 1872, Aug. 2.Hannah W. Hitchcock to Seymour W. Nash. Thanks for money for Erminia's funeral.
  - 19.a 1872, Oct. [29].Thaxter Poole to Seymour W. Nash. Family history.
    [UNK] 190
  - 20. 1873, Jan. 24.C. W. Underwood to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 21. 1873, Jan. 26.[Deborah W. Knowles?] to [S. W. Nash]. Opinion of Oneida by outsiders, reminiscences.
  - 22. 1873, Feb. 9.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash. Article in Circular on Grandfather Nash, asks about family history, Elinor.
  - 23. 1873, Feb. 25.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash. Family history.
  - 24. 1873, Mar. 23.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. 70 yrs. old.
  - 25. 1873, Apr. 23.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 26. 1873, May 13.Olive Ann Nash to Seymour W. Nash. Duties, news.
  - 27. 1873, June 22.Deborah Knowles to S. W. Nash.
  - 28. 1873, June 22.W. Atwood Knowles to S. W. Nash.
  - 29. 1873, July 4.Etta [Knowles] to [Seymour W. Nash].
  - 30. 1873, July 27.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash.
  - 31. 1873, Dec. 16.W[illiam] S. Knowles to [Russel Knowles].
  - 32. 1874, Jan. 23.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash].
  - 33. 1874, Feb. 13.W. Atwood Knowles to S. W. Nash. Deborah very ill.
  - 34. [1874?], Mar. 20.W. Atwood Knowles to [S. W. Nash]. Deborah died.
  - 35. 1874, Apr. 2.Wealthy A. Knowles to [S. W. Nash]. With photo of Russel Knowles.
  - 36. 1874, July 21.[Joel Higgins] to Seymour W. Nash. Message from a seance?
    7/23
  - 37. 1874, July 23.E. Higgins to Seymour W. Nash. Explains #36.
  - 38. 1874, Nov. 27.Wealthy A. Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. 47th wedding anniversary.
  - 39. 1875, Jan. 16.George Campbell to S. W. Nash.
  - 40. 1875, Apr. 3.W. Atwood Knowles to [S. W. Nash].
  - 41. 1875, Apr. 11.Ellen A. Knowles to [S. W. Nash?].
  - 42. 1875, June 15.Ellen A. Knowles to Seymour [W. Nash].
  - 43. 1875, Jul. 18.Wealthy A. Knowles to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 44. 1875, Aug. 15.Etta Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash].
  - 45. 1875, Oct. 4.Etta Knowles to Seymour [W. Nash].
  - 46. [1875].W. Atwood Knowles to [S. W. Nash et al].
  - 47. 1876, Jan. 7.Wealthy A. Knowles to [S. W. Nash].
  - 48. 1876, Jan. 25.Edwin S. Spaulding to Beloved ones. Death of his father.
  - 49. 1876, Mar. 21.Wealthy A. Knowles to [S. W. Nash].
  - 50. 1876, Jul. 24.L. L. Burt to S. W. Nash. Harriet Howard & John Cragin - question over child, Mr. Thayer's son, Mrs. Matthews.
  - 51. 1876, Nov. 1.George D. Allen to [S. W. Nash?]. About watches.
  - 52. 1876, Dec. [15].Mary R. Jones to S. W. Nash. Mr. Seymour and Victor.
- 1877-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1. 1877, Mar. 7.Wealthy A. Knowles to [S. W. Nash].
  - 2. 1877, Apr. 4.Wealthy A. Knowles to [S. W. Nash]. Sugar making, brother Daniel.
  - 3. 1877, June 10.[Fanny M.?] Leonard to S. [W.] Nash.
  - 4. 1877, June 23.S. A. Story to S. W. Nash. Mary's daughter born dead.
  - 5. 1877, Jul. 2.S. A. Story to S. W. Nash. Mary not to have more children.
  - 6. 1877, Jul. 28.S. A. Story to [S. W.] Nash. Death of her father & older sister, no hope of children.
  - 7. 1877, Jul. 30.A. C. Sears to S. W. Nash. Foundation of new house at Oneida.
  - 8. 1877, Aug. 19.[Fanny M.?] Leonard to [S. W.] Nash. Mary Jones, Victor leaves Community.
  - 9. 1877, Sept. 6.[Charles] Olds to [S. W. Nash].
  - 10. 1877, Sept. 6.S. W. Nash to Carrie A. [MacNett?]. At Litchfield for hayfever.
  - 11. 1877, Sept. 6.Carrie A. [MacNett of Macknett?] to S. W. Nash. Letter from Edwin Nash.
  - 12. 1877, Sept. 8.S. W. Nash to Carrie A. Macknett. Old cemetary at Litchfield.
  - 13. 1877, Sept. 13.S. W. Nash to Carrie [A. Macknett].
  - 14. 1877, Sept. 14.F. R. Leonard to S. W. Nash. Seymour's hayfever from ragweed.
  - 15. 1877, Sept. 18.[Charles] Olds to [S. W. Nash]. Martin's fall, Alice Ackley's new son.
  - 16. 1877, Sept. 20.S. W. Nash to Carrie A. [Macknett].
  - 17. 1877, [?] 13.[Mary R. Jones] to S. W. Nash. (M. L. Prindle?).
    1/10/78
  - 18. 1878, June 18.Carrie A. [Macknett] to S. W. Nash.
  - 19. 1878, June 19.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash. About his room.
    9/16
  - 20. [1878], June 21.Jane ? A [UNK] to S. W. Nash.
    10/3
  - 21. 1878, Jul. 13.[H. A. W.] to [S. W.] Nash.
  - 22. 1878, Jul. 28.Egbert P. Knowles to S. W. Nash.
  - 23. 1878, Aug. 1.W[illiam] H.[Woolworth] to S. W. Nash. Work at Wallingford.
  - 24. 1878, Aug. 9.Egbert P. Knowles & Ellen A. Knowles to S. W. Nash. Father's (Atwood) death.
  - 25. 1878, Aug. 20.G. W. R[eeve] to [S. W.] Nash. Tornado or hurricane of Aug. 9 at Wallingford.
  - 26. 1878, Aug. 21.W[illiam] H. Woolworth to [S. W.] Nash. Tornado, destruction.
  - 27. 1878, Aug. 21.E[lizabeth] Whitfield to S. W. Nash.
  - 28. 1878, Aug. 21.E[lizabeth] G. Hawley to S. W. Nash.
  - 29. 1878, Aug. 21.Ellen Nash to S. W. Nash.
  - 30. 1878, Aug. 21.Mary Louise [UNK] to S. W. Nash.
  - 31. 1878, Dec. 15.Ellen Nash to S. W. Nash. Seymour's accident.
  - 32. 1879, Jan. 27.Edwin S. Spaulding to [S. W. Nash]. Death of his mother (1878).
  - 33. 1879, Apr. 6.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash. Seymour at Wallingford, Evan & Ellen.
  - 34. 1879, May 17.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash. Uncle Edwin's land claim.
  - 35. 1879, July 8.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash. Ellen's health.
  - 36. 1879, Aug. 23.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash.
  - 37. [1879, Aug. 30].Lunch Packer to Dear Miss: Printed note, name of Miss H. [[UNK]]. Brooks appears on verso (sister of E. R. Nash by his mother's first husband).
    [UNK] 10/19
  - 38. 1879, Oct. 30.Seth Reed to Daniel [Pool] Nash. Writing history & geneology of Edwin Poole and descendents.
  - 39. 1879, Dec. 17.Olive Ann Nash to S. W. Nash. To be married to Otis [Kellogg]. [UNK]
  - 40. [1879?].William Henry Channing. My Symphony. Handwritten copy on Wallingford Printing Company letterhead.
  - 41. 1880, Jan. 2.Olive Nash Kellogg to S. W. Nash. Wedding, Ellen.
  - 42. 1880, Jan. 3.Wealthy A. Knowles to Seymour W. Nash. Paper stopped, change in social platform (end of complex marriage).
  - 43. 1880, Jan. 8.Seth Reed to Seymour W. Nash. Necessity of dates in family record.
  - 44. 1880, Feb. 1.Etta G. Knowles to [S. W. Nash?].
  - 45. 1880, Feb. 5.Olive Nash Kellogg to S. W. Nash. A watch for Alice, wedding, Edwin S. Spaulding was married.
  - 46. 1880, Feb. 14.Olive Nash Kellogg to S. W. Nash. Alice's marriage, Chloe Richards.
  - 47. 1880, Mar. 31.Ellen Nash to S. W. Nash. Seymour's proposal turned down by Miss S., personal
  - 48. 1880, Apr. 19.Ellen Nash to S. W. Nash.
  - 49. 1880, May 16.Olive Nash Kellogg to S. W. Nash. With line from Emma.
  - 50. 1880. Spring.D. E. Hoxie. Printed price list for small fruit plants and etc.
  - 51. 1881, Jan. [15].Ellen Nash to S. W. Nash. Number of people ill, beginning of joint stock, Walter.
  - 52. 1882, Mar. 17.Alice E. Sears (niece?) to S. W. Nash. Walter Thayer.
  - 53.a 1884, Apr. 23.Edwin S. Spaulding to Dear Cousin. Asks for family dates including death date of Seymour [W. Nash].
    9/16/36 8/18/01 [UNK] [UNK] 53d. 53e. [UNK]
  - 54. 1903, Sept. 12.J[ames] W[illiam] Towner to Dear nephew.
  - 55. [1907], Apr. 8.William A. Hinds to Evan Rupert Nash. Community news.
  - 56. 1909,S[tephen] R. Leonard to Evan R. Nash. Oneida Community, Limited.
  - 57. 1918, Dec. 17.Rockwell A. Barnes to [Carrie Stewart]. From Speicher, Germany, armistice, battles, Belgium welcome.
  - 58-62. [1918].Germany annotated by R. A. Barnes., 5 postcards of Speicher
  - 63. 1934, Oct. 3.Amos Reeve to Evan Rupert Nash. Sister Carrie's diary, Horatio Temple Noyes married Nora of Leonora Hatch.
  - 64. 1945, Jan.Eleonor Kellogg Herrick to Evan R. Nash. Daughter of Olive Nash Kellogg. Family news.
- UNDATED (Box 1, Folder 8)
  (alphabetical arrangement)
  - 1. N.D.S. to S. W. Nash. Failing of respect.
  - 2. Mar. 11.[Elmira] Fadeley to Seymour W. Nash. Asks for money, envelope has S.W.N. note.
  - 3. N.D. [Sept.?].Tryphena Freeman to Dear Sister. Plans visit, John to teach, Schenectady.
  - 4. Aug. 11.Deborah [W. Knowles] to Unknown. Fragment or postscript. Atwood, thanks [UNK] for taking care of him while he was ill.
  - 5. July.Ellen [Knowles] to Seymour [W. Nash]. From Walmouth, [Atwood].
  - 6. Aug. 29.W. Atwood Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. Champion. Wants to go to Community, Deborah.
  - 7. Monday, Sept. 17.W. Atwood Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Since leaving Community, health, trying to find place for winter, Egbert, has not seen Wealthy yet.
  - 8. Sept. 16.W. Atwood Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. Pinkney. Bought Albert Thompson's place, needs money owed him by Community, postscript from Barnes Corners.
  - 9. Aug. 10.W. Atwood Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. Champion. Egbert, Sarah, etc., family & occupation.
  - 10. Aug. 20.W. Atwood Knowles to [Seymour W. Nash]. Champion. Deborah, Sarah, note to Sarah.
  - 11. May [7].W. Atwood Knowles to Seymour W. Nash. Champion. Sent $2800 to Mr. Campbell (Community), plans to arrive at Community in June.
  - 12. Feb. 20.W. Atwood Knowles to [Sarah B. Nash]. Champion. Health, Deborah, snow, Egbert.
  - 13. N.D.Wealthy [A. Knowles] to [Sarah B. Nash]. Return from Community, Russel's reception.
  - 14. N.D.William S. Knowles. The Indian Hunter. Poem sent to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 15.[UNK] Sept. 30.Edwin S. Nash to [Uriah Church]. Left Hamilton to work on Sherburne Transcript.
  - 16. N.D.Ellen [Nash] to Father Nash., Note.
  - 17. Monday, June 21.Sophia [Church] Nash to [Mr. & Mrs. Uriah Church]. Mr. Clark, Mr. Ackley, invitation, Daniel still in Brooklyn.
  - 18. N.D.M[artha?] S. R[eeve] to S. W. Nash. Fragment, criticism.
  - 19. July 23.H[enry] Thacker to S. W. Nash. Mildew, grapes and dusting.
  - 20. Oct. 11.[Henry Thacker] to S. W. Nash. Putting up apples without sugar.
  - 21. Nov.E[lizabeth] Whitfield to S. W. Nash. Mrs. Nash so bright and happy, to visit Putney.
- SARAH B. NASH'S LETTERS TO S. W. NASH FROM WALLINGFORD
  - 22. May 1, Sunday.Health, Mrs. Miller, Mr. Kelly, Mrs. Sears, can't travel to Meridon to have photo taken, Mrs. B[urt] note.
  - 23. July 31.Letter to Wealthy, ride with Mr. Kellogg & Margaret, Mr. Noyes fishing, Mr. Olds, Mr. Zelly left, Mrs. Miller, Mrs. Tuttle & H.W.H.
  - 24. Nov. 10. Rained little since you were here, Mrs. T., Fidelia has taken Frederic, Mr. Ackley homesick, Mr. Barron & Mr. Thayer pedling horse radish, note by Bedy Tuttle.
  - 25. Nov. 21.Mr. Cragin ill, love to Mrs. Burt, asks about Florilla, plans Thanksgiving.
  - 26. Nov. 26, Friday.Day after Thanksgiving, Seymour had been at Kirk Vill, Seymour's mother?, flannel shirts in Olive Ann's chest, Seymour's picture.
  - 27. Dec. 1.Mr. Carr, theatricals, Abby, Seymour's mother, Mr. Perry, Sarah Campbell.
  - 28. Saturday, Dec. 11.Health, Mrs. Clark is her nurse, part torn off and something erased.
  - 29. Dec. 12.Health, Mrs. Hatch, Mr. Thayer visiting O.C., Mrs. Miller going to O.C.
  - 30. Dec. 18.Mr. T., Mrs. Clark and Mrs. Tuttle, Abby's baby, Mr. Cragin, Mrs. Thayer, G. W. Noyes wrote to Fidelia.
- SARAH B. NASH TO SEYMOUR W. NASH. N.D.N.P.
  - 31. N.D.S.B.C[ampbell?] dinner for Mrs. Miller who is leaving for a visit, Mary & baby, Margaret.
  - 32. Dear Brother. Men, love and courting.
  - Cake of sugar, Seymour ill?, Mrs. Cragin says
  - 34. Poem, no title, unsigned.
  - 35. Sweet potato, ask Mrs. Burt to cook it, Mr. Thayer to be gone.
  - 36. Mr. Leonard fat, stockings, Mrs. Robinson.
  - 37. Cover sheet for a letter.
  - 38. Work in the kitchen, Philenia, Louisa, Mrs. Abbott, Mrs. Hull, Emma, brother Daniel, sends thanks to Mr. Smith and Mrs. Inslee, Fanny, Daniel Knowles, Mr. Olds, Mr. Macknett.
  - 39. Ellen well and happy, learning to read.
    NOTE: The following letters are interfiled with those listed on pages 1 - 14.
- 1827 - 1859 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1. 1853, Aug. 11.Sarah B. Nash to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 2. 1853, Sep. 30.Daniel P. Nash to Edwin.
  - 3. 1853, Nov. 10.Daniel P. Nash to Edwin.
  - 4. 1854, Aug. 7.Sarah B. Nash to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 5. 1859, May 22.Sarah B. Nash to Dear Brother.
- 1860 - 1862 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1. 1860, Feb. 25.Sarah B. Nash to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 2. 1862, May [10].Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
- 1864 - 1865 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1. 1864, June 17.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 2. 1864, July 10.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Brother & Sister.
  - 3. 1865, Sept.John S. Freeman to My Dear Brother.
- 1866 - 1869 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1. 1867, Jan. 5.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 2. 1867, Mar. 15.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 3. 1867, Apr. 1.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 4. 1867, June 9.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 5. 1867, Aug. 20.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Brother.
  - 6. 1867, Sep. 1.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 7. 1868, Mar. 5.no sig. to Dear Sister.
- 1870 - 1876 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1. [18]70, Mar. 15.Erminia N. Worcester to My dear brother.
  - 2. 1870, June 27.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 3. 1870, Sep. 15.Erminia N. Worcester to My dear brother.
  - 4. 1871, July 30.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Sister.
  - 5. 1872, May 26.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Brother.
  - 6. 1873, Jan. 18.Alice Eva to My Dear Uncle [Seymour W. Nash].
  - 7. 1876, July 23.Ellen to Dear Uncle.
- 1877 - 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1. 1877, Apr. 24.Father to Percy.
  - 2. 1877, July 26.F.U.L. (Leonard) to Mr. Nash.
  - 3. 1877, Sep. 6.E. Whitfield to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 4. 1877, Sep. 13+16.Seymour W. Nash to Carrie A. [Morknett].
  - 5. 1877, Sep. 18.E. Whitfield to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 6. 1877, Oct. 3.Wealthy A. Knowles to Seymour W. Nash.
  - 7. 1878, Jan. 10.Telegram to Edwin S. Nash from G. N. Miller.
  - 8. 1878, Aug. 23.Wealthy A. Knowles to Dear Brother.
  - 9. 1879, Sep. 17.T. Poole to Dear Nephew.
  - 10. 1879, Oct. 19.F.U. Leonard to Brother Nash.
  - 11. 1881, Nov. 22.Sister Frank to Dear Sister.
  - 12. 1886, Sep. 16.Evan Rupert from his mother.
  - 13. 1900 - 1901.Sketch for a motorcycle by E.R. Nash.
  - 14. 1905, Mar. 16.Dept. of Interior to Mrs. Edwin S. Nash (Martha S. Nash) - certificat
  - 15. [1906], Sep. 18.O.A. Kellogg to Evan.
  - 16. [UNK]
- UNDATED (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1. Knowles, Wealthy A. Page 5 of letter to unknown.
  - 2. Muzzy, Mercy M. Certificate to Edwin Nash for good scholarship with cvr.
- SARAH B. NASH'S LETTERS TO S.W. NASH FROM WALLINGFORD
  - 1. Oct. 21.
  - 2. Dec. 4.
- SARAH B. NASH TO SEYMOUR W. NASH; N.D.,N.P.
  - 1. Friday morning.
- Additions to Nash Family Collection
  NOTE: The following additions are interfiled with the letters listed on pages 1-14.
  - 31b. 1859, Nov. 27.Edwin S. Nash to Mr. and Mrs. Uriah Church. Copy of #31a and partial copy of #5 in folder 2. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 15b. 1864, June 13.olive Nash to My Dear Brother [E.S. Nash]. Plan to build a university at Wallingford, meditation or reflection. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 15d. 1864, June 19.Olive [Nash] to Edwin [S. Nash]. Personal, Mr. George Noyes.
  - 16b. [1864] June.Florilla [Nash] to [Edwin S. Nash]. Personal.
  - 17b. 1864, July 4.Olive [Nash] to [Edwin S. Nash]. Personal, ride.
  - 17c. 1864, July 4.Rillie [Florilla Nash] to Edwin [S. Nash]. Horseback ride, handwriting.
  - 19b. 1864, July 20.Olive [Nash] to [Edwin S. Nash]. Re: his printed letters, sending things like stationary, Harriet Worden, George Kellogg.
  - 19c. 1864, July 20.Rillie [Florilla Nash] to Edwin [S. Nash]. Personal.
  - 19d. 1864, July 20.Theo. L. P[i[UNK]] to [Edwin S. Nash]
  - 20b. 1864, Sept, 1.Pass to [E.S.] Nash, signed by A.N. H[UNK].
  - 20c. 1864, Sept. 4.Olive [Nash] to [Edwin S. Nash]. William Watson ill.
  - 20d. 1864, Sept. 5.Rillie [Florilla Nash] to Edwin [S. Nash]. Baking.
  - 20e. 1864, Sept 10.Olive [Nash] to [Edwin S. Nash] with a note added by Rillie. Thinking about seeing Edwin again.
  - 23b. 1864, Nov. 13.O[live Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Arrival of Mr. Noyes, article about Mr. Mills.
  - 23c. 1864, Dec, 17.Olive [Nash] to Edwin S. Nash.
  - 23d. 1864, Dec. 21.Rillie [Florilla Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Sleigh ride.
  - 24b. 1865, Jan. 2.Olive [Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Studies, sleigh ride, family news.
  - 27b. 1865, Feb. 4.Rillie [Florilla Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Mr. Noyes plan, personal.
  - 25b. 1867, Nov. 2.Ellen [Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Personal. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 28b. 1867, Dec. 30.[E. S. Nash]. General Statement of Business of Job Office for the year 1867.
  - 28c. 1867, Dec. 31.E. S. Nash to Mssrs. Parker. Order for paper for Wallingford Community.
  - 28d. 1868, Jan. 1.[E.S. Nash] Inventory of Printing Office.
  - 30b. 1868, March 7.[E.S. Nash] Inventory of Printing Office.
  - 33b. 1868, Nov. 5.Rillie [Florilla Nash] to Edwin S. Nash. Personal.
  - 19b. 1872.Copy of Bounty Land Act of 1872 in the hand of Edwin S. Nash. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 53b. 1900, Nov. 7.Everett Lesley to Evan R. Nash. Inquiry about results of accident to Nash. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 53d. 1901, Aug. 18.Harriet Walling to Dear Friend [E. R. Nash] Personal, discouraging feelings other than friendship.
  - 53e. [1901], Sept. 4.Mother to Evan [Rupert] Nash. Sympathy and advice.
  - 53f. 1902, Aug. 13.Harriet Walling to Evan R. Nash. Personal.
  - 54b. 1905, Jan. 9. Nursery Mom [E. R. Nash's mother] to My very dear children [Envelope addressed to E. R. Nash]. Personal, and yogi exercises.
  - 54c. 1905, Jan. 16. Pa [Nash] to Ev[an R. Nash].
  - 54d. 1905, Jan. 19.Mother [Nash] to Children dear [addressed to E. R. Nash]. Personal.
  - 56b. 1909, Dec. 28.H. N. Herrick to E. R. Nash. Analysis of flux.
  - 56c. 1918, Apr. 24.Deming [UNK] to E. R. Nash., Postcard.
  - 62b. 1919, Aug. 26.Harrie [Mrs. E. R. Nash] to E. R. Nash., Postcard.
  - 62c. 1919, Oct. 1.Jim [a nephew] to E. R. Nash., Postcard.
  - 62d. 1920, Dec. 28.The Tabers to E. R. Nash., Postcard.
  - 62e. 1921, March 13.Dorothy Nash to Daddy [E. R. Nash].
  - 62f. 1921, April 10.Dorothy Nash to Daddy [E. R. Nash].
  - 62g. 1921, April 15.Don (?) to Dad [E. R. Nash].
  - 62h. 1921, Apr. 23.Ivan [Nash] and [Mrs. Nash] to Daddy [E. R. Nash].
  - 62i. 1921, April 28.Dorothy Nash to Daddy [E. R. Nash].
  - 62j. [1921]Description of a bullfrog. Enclosed with 62e-i in one envelope to E. R. Nash.
  - 62l. 1923, July 9.Mother to [E. R. Nash].
  - 62m. 1923, July 13.Hilda [Herrick Noyes] to Evan [Rupert Nash]. Stirpiculture.
  - 3b. July 9.E & W Grocery to Evan [R. Nash]. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 14b. Dorothy [Nash] to Daddy [E. R. Nash]., Postcard.
  - 15b. [Edwin S. Nash]. Estimated Cost of Publishing the Circular for one year.
  - 15c. Edwin S. Nash. About his membership in the Community.
  - 15d. Edwin S. Nash to Mr. Hamilton about his [Nash's] application for membership in the Oneida Community.
  - 16b. Aug. 21.Ivan [Nash] to Dad [E. R. Nash]., Postcard.
  - 16c. Ivan [Nash] to Daddy [E. R. Nash]., Postcard.
  - 16d. Rillie [Florilla Nash] to [Edwin S. Nash].
  - 17b. Hilda [Herrick Noyes] to [Evan R. Nash]. Page 1 missing.
  - Printed Material (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1. The Circular, July 11, 1864.Printed letter of Edwin Nash written June 12, 1864 to Dear Friends., Clipping.